[A Mission of the Heart]
[مهمة القلب]
[Episode 17]
[الحلقة 17]
Officer Huang must have been hit
لا بد أن الضابط هوانغ قد أصيب
with the Weakness Powder.
مع مسحوق الضعف.
It doesn't just cause fatigue.
فهو لا يسبب التعب فقط.
It also has aphrodisiac and hallucinogenic effects.
كما أن لها تأثيرات مثيرة للشهوة ومسببة للهلوسة.
That filthy Taoist!
هذا الطاوي القذر!
If he dares to lay a finger on Yu,
إذا تجرأ على وضع إصبعه على يو،
I'll skin him alive!
سأسلخه حيًا!
It has only been a moment.
لقد كانت لحظة واحدة فقط.
She must still be in the temple.
لا بد أنها لا تزال في المعبد.
Zhao, Mao,
تشاو، ماو،
you two search the outside.
أنتما الاثنان تبحثان في الخارج.
Shen Pan and I will check the inside.
أنا و شين بان سوف نتحقق من الداخل.
-Yes.
-نعم.
Shen Pan.
شين بان.
How's it going?
كيف الحال؟
My Lord.
سيدي.
We've searched everywhere,
لقد بحثنا في كل مكان،
but we found nothing.
ولكننا لم نجد شيئا.
Impossible.
مستحيل.
That's impossible!
هذا مستحيل!
This Changsheng Temple isn't very large.
هذا المعبد تشانغشنغ ليس كبيرًا جدًا.
To hide someone in such a short time,
إخفاء شخص ما في مثل هذا الوقت القصير،
there must be a secret passage or chamber.
لا بد أن يكون هناك ممر أو غرفة سرية.
Keep searching.
استمر في البحث.
Even if we have to turn the whole temple upside down,
حتى لو كان علينا أن نقلب المعبد بأكمله رأسًا على عقب،
we must find her!
يجب علينا أن نجدها!
If we can't find her here,
إذا لم نتمكن من العثور عليها هنا،
expand the search into the mountains.
توسيع نطاق البحث في الجبال.
Keep looking!
استمر بالبحث!
Yes.
نعم.
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
We know nothing about her background.
نحن لا نعرف شيئا عن خلفيتها.
She's not even on our list.
إنها ليست حتى في قائمتنا.
You shouldn't have kidnapped her.
لا ينبغي لك أن تختطفها.
I have already checked it.
لقد قمت بفحصه بالفعل.
There's absolutely no problem.
لا توجد مشكلة على الإطلاق.
But...
لكن...
No buts.
لا يوجد أي استثناءات.
If that lord hadn't
لو لم يكن هذا الرب
accidentally killed Mrs. Chen,
قتل السيدة تشين عن طريق الخطأ،
I wouldn't
انا لن افعل
have resorted to such a move.
لقد لجأوا إلى مثل هذه الخطوة.
Without the list provided by Mrs. Chen,
بدون القائمة التي قدمتها السيدة تشين،
I have to find my own way.
يجب علي أن أجد طريقي بنفسي.
Our plan cannot stop.
خطتنا لا يمكن أن تتوقف.
If it stops,
إذا توقفت،
all our previous efforts will be for nothing.
كل جهودنا السابقة ستذهب سدى.
Can you afford
هل تستطيع تحمل التكلفة؟
that responsibility?
تلك المسؤولية؟
Then be careful.
إذن كن حذرا.
My little beauty,
جمالي الصغير
let me
دعني
give you some real pleasure.
سأمنحك بعض المتعة الحقيقية.
I promise I'll make
أعدك بأنني سأفعل
you pregnant.
انت حامل.
This isn't Lord Lu.
هذا ليس اللورد لو.
Ms. Huang?
السيدة هوانغ؟
Miss Ziyan?
آنسة زيان؟
Why are you here?
لماذا انت هنا؟
I got caught by them while trying
لقد تم القبض علي من قبلهم أثناء محاولتي
to uncover the truth for my sister.
لكشف الحقيقة لأختي.
Now is not the time to talk about this.
الآن ليس الوقت المناسب للحديث عن هذا.
You...
أنت...
You go get that girl
اذهب واحصل على تلك الفتاة
and bring her back.
وأعيدها.
Since you've already exposed yourself,
بما أنك قد كشفت نفسك بالفعل،
there's no need for you to live anymore!
لم تعد هناك حاجة لعيشك بعد الآن!
Let's go!
دعنا نذهب!
The Taoist is dead. Let's escape now!
مات الطاوي. لنهرب الآن!
He's dead?
هل هو ميت؟
Thank goodness!
شكرا لله
Follow me. I know where the exit is.
اتبعني، أنا أعرف أين المخرج.
Let's go!
دعنا نذهب!
Be careful!
احرص!
The old bastard died just like this?
هل مات الرجل العجوز بهذه الطريقة؟
He really didn't suffer enough.
إنه لم يعاني بما فيه الكفاية.
We need to find Yu as quickly as possible.
نحن بحاجة إلى العثور على يو في أسرع وقت ممكن.
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
Hurry!
عجل!
Ziyan, take this.
زيان، خذ هذا.
I'm leaving their safety in your hands now.
أنا أترك سلامتهم بين يديك الآن.
What about you?
ماذا عنك؟
Don't worry. I'm from the Imperial Guard.
لا تقلق، أنا من الحرس الإمبراطوري.
I'll take care of myself.
سأعتني بنفسي.
Take care of them.
اعتني بهم.
Be careful!
احرص!
Stop running!
توقف عن الجري!
Hurry!
عجل!
Stop!
قف!
Lord Shen?
اللورد شين؟
It's Lord Shen!
إنه اللورد شين!
Miss Ziyan.
السيدة زيان.
Why isn't Huang Yu with you?
لماذا هوانغ يو ليس معك؟
To protect us, Ms. Huang
لحمايتنا، السيدة هوانغ
lured those people away by herself.
أغوت هؤلاء الأشخاص بعيدًا بنفسها.
My Lord.
سيدي.
Zhao, take them back.
تشاو، خذهم مرة أخرى.
Yes.
نعم.
Mao,
لذا،
escort them to a safe place.
رافقهم إلى مكان آمن.
I'll go find Yu.
سأذهب للبحث عن يو.
Yes, My Lord.
نعم سيدي.
Huang Yu!
هوانغ يو!
How's it going?
كيف الحال؟
I still haven't found them.
ولم أجدهم بعد.
My Lord.
سيدي.
What about you?
ماذا عنك؟
No sign of Lord Lu and Officer Huang.
لا يوجد أي أثر للسيد لو والضابط هوانغ.
Send more men.
أرسل المزيد من الرجال.
Find them at all costs.
ابحث عنهم بأي ثمن.
Yes.
نعم.
It hurts.
إنه يؤلمني.
-Yu. -It hurts.
-يو. -إنه يؤلم.
Bear with it a little longer.
تحملها لفترة أطول قليلا.
I'll pull the arrow out for you first.
سأخرج السهم لك أولاً.
I'll apply medicine for you.
سأطبق عليك الطب.
♪ The trace engraved upon my heart ♪
♪ الأثر المنقوش على قلبي ♪
♪ Grows clearer each time I dream ♪
♪ يصبح الأمر أكثر وضوحًا في كل مرة أحلم فيها ♪
♪ So familiar ♪
♪ مألوفة جدا ♪
♪ Yet forever out of reach ♪
♪ ومع ذلك فهي بعيدة عن متناول اليد إلى الأبد ♪
♪ Beautiful as a mirage ♪
♪ جميلة كالسراب ♪
♪ My thoughts are soaked through with ink ♪
♪ أفكاري غارقة بالحبر ♪
♪ Yet I don't know where to start ♪
♪ ولكنني لا أعرف من أين أبدأ ♪
♪ If hearts could draw each other near, no distance could stand between ♪
♪ لو استطاعت القلوب أن تقترب من بعضها البعض، فلن تقف أي مسافة بينها ♪
Yu,
يو،
bear with it.
تحملها.
♪ You are the one thing I'm sure of ♪
♪ أنت الشيء الوحيد الذي أنا متأكد منه ♪
It hurts!
إنه يؤلمني!
♪ As the gentle rain falls endlessly ♪
♪ بينما يهطل المطر اللطيف بلا نهاية ♪
Yu.
يو.
♪ I keep thinking about you ♪
♪ أنا أستمر في التفكير بك ♪
♪ I spend my whole life remembering ♪
♪ أقضي حياتي كلها في التذكر ♪
♪ So brief our meetings, so long our partings ♪
♪ كانت لقاءاتنا قصيرة، وفراقنا طويل ♪
Yu!
يو!
♪ Fate always comes too late ♪
♪ القدر يأتي دائما متأخرا ♪
Yu,
يو،
you successfully rescued those women.
لقد نجحت في انقاذ هؤلاء النساء.
♪ Hiding again and again ♪
♪ الاختباء مرارا وتكرارا ♪
What reward do you want?
ما هي المكافأة التي تريدها؟
♪ Sighing again and again ♪
♪ التنهد مرارا وتكرارا ♪
Whatever I want...
كل ما أريده...
♪ Who's saying sorry? ♪
♪ من يقول آسف؟ ♪
would be okay?
هل سيكون على ما يرام؟
♪ Everything falls to silence as the moon rises ♪
♪ كل شيء يسوده الصمت عندما يرتفع القمر ♪
As long as you can say it,
طالما يمكنك أن تقول ذلك،
♪ Love paints your face upon the night ♪
♪ الحب يرسم وجهك على الليل ♪
of course it's okay.
بالطبع لا بأس.
I want...
أريد...
♪ Rippling softly ♪
♪ تموج بهدوء ♪
you...
أنت...
Yu.
يو.
Yu!
يو!
Lu Zhan!
لو زان!
My Lord.
سيدي.
Zhao,
تشاو،
hurry and examine Yu!
اسرعوا وفحصوا يو!
Okay.
تمام.
How is Yu doing?
كيف حال يو؟
She's not well.
إنها ليست بخير.
What do you mean by that?
ماذا تقصد بذلك؟
After suffering severe injuries,
بعد تعرضه لإصابات خطيرة،
Yu was soaked in water.
كان يو غارقًا في الماء.
And now she has a persistent high fever.
والآن تعاني من ارتفاع مستمر في درجة الحرارة.
If this continues,
إذا استمر هذا،
I'm afraid she might...
أخشى أنها قد...
That won't happen!
هذا لن يحدث!
Yu will be fine.
سيكون بخير.
Zhao.
تشاو.
Last time,
آخر مرة،
I asked you to investigate
لقد طلبت منك التحقيق
if there's any connection between Jiang Ning and Yu.
إذا كان هناك أي صلة بين جيانج نينغ ويو.
You said there wasn't any.
قلت أنه لا يوجد أي شيء.
Focus on investigating
التركيز على التحقيق
what Jiang Ning did
ما فعله جيانغ نينغ
before Yu turned 5 years old.
قبل أن يبلغ يو 5 سنوات من عمره.
Yes.
نعم.
Yu.
يو.
Yu, it's me.
يو، أنا.
It's me, Yu.
أنا، يو.
My Lord.
سيدي.
Yu.
يو.
I'm here.
أنا هنا.
It's all over now.
لقد انتهى كل شيء الآن.
You'll be alright, Yu.
ستكون بخير، يو.
I'm here.
أنا هنا.
Everything's fine now.
كل شئ على ما يرام الآن.
Don't be afraid.
لا تخف.